{
  "minecraft-version": "Minecraft weergawe",
  "plugin-load-problem": "Die plugin '{{plugin-name}}' kon nie gelaai word nie.",
  "pocketmine-version": "Pocketmine weergawe",
  "bedrock-version": "Bedrock weergawe",
  "forge-version": "Forge weergawe",
  "authme-shutdown-problem": "Die plugin 'AuthMe' misluk en sluit die server af.",
  "pex-config-problem": "Die opset van die plugin 'PermissionsEx' is ongeldig.",
  "ambiguous-plugin-name-problem": "Daar is verskeie plugin-lÃªers vir die inpropnaam '{{plugin-name}}': '{{first-plugin-path}}' en '{{second-plugin-path}}'.",
  "plugin-dependency-problem": "Die plugin '{{plugin-name}}' ontbreek die vereiste die inprop '{{dependency-plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-disabling-problem": "Die inprop '{{plugin-name}}' kon nie gedeaktiveer word nie.",
  "plugin-enabling-problem": "Die inprop '{{plugin-name}}' kon nie gedeaktiveer word nie.",
  "plugin-runtime-problem": "Die plugin '{{plugin-name}}' het 'n probleem tydens hardloop.",
  "forge-confirm-problem": "U moet bevestig dat u veranderinge moet toepas en die bediener moet begin.",
  "mod-dependency-problem": "Die mod '{{mod-name}}' ontbreek die vereiste mod {{dependency-mod-name}}.",
  "mod-dependency-problem-plural": "Die mod '{{mod-name}}' ontbreek die vereiste mods {{dependency-mod-list}}.",
  "mod-duplicate-problem": "There are multiple mod files for the mod name '{{mod-name}}': '{{first-mod-path}}' and '{{second-mod-path}}'.",
  "mod-exception-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' has thrown an exception.",
  "mod-fatal-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' has a fatal error.",
  "world-missing-mod-problem": "The world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' which appears to be missing.",
  "world-mod-version-problem": "This world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' version {{mod-expected-version}} and it is now at version {{mod-current-version}}.",
  "plugin-incompatible-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' is incompatible with your current server version.",
  "aquatic-world-on-older-version-problem": "The current world was created/loaded with Minecraft 1.13 or higher. The new format cannot be loaded in any older version.",
  "old-player-directory-problem": "The server has detected an old player directory in the world save.",
  "command-run-solution": "Run the command '{{command}}'.",
  "authme-shutdown-solution": "Stel 'stopServer' op 'true'.",
  "configure-plugin": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}}.",
  "configure-plugin-with-file": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}} ({{suggested-file}}).",
  "plugin-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different version of the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-install-solution": "Install the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-remove-solution": "Remove the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "file-delete-solution": "Delete the file '{{file-path}}'.",
  "file-edit-solution": "Edit the file '{{file-path}}'.",
  "mod-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different version of the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution": "Install the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution-with-version": "Install the mod '{{mod-name}}' with version {{mod-version}}.",
  "mod-remove-solution": "Remove the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "aquatic-version-install-solution": "Update the server software to 1.13 or newer.",
  "plugin-command-exception-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' cannot execute the command '{{command}}'.",
  "ticking-block-entity-problem": "A block in the world is causing problems.",
  "remove-block-solution": "Remove the block from the world, e.g. with MCEdit.",
  "do-nothing-solution": "Do nothing. This problem might fix itself.",
  "chunk-load-exception-problem": "There was an exception while loading the world chunks.",
  "remove-chunk-solution": "Remove the problematic chunk from the world, e.g. with MCEdit or by removing the region file.",
  "multiverse-load-problem": "The world '{{world-name}}' could not be loaded because it contains errors and is probably corrupt.",
  "world-repair-solution": "Repair the world '{{world-name}}', e.g. by using Minecraft Region Fixer or MCEdit.",
  "world-duplicate-problem": "World '{{world-name}}' is a duplicate of another world and has been prevented from loading.",
  "mod-wrong-minecraft-version-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is not compatible with the Minecraft version {{minecraft-version}}.",
  "forge-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different Forge version.",
  "malformed-encoding-problem": "Something (probably the MOTD) contains malformed formatting codes.",
  "change-motd-solution": "Change the server MOTD.",
  "bedrock-authentication-whitelist-problem": "Using a whitelist without online authentication is not allowed.",
  "disable-whitelist-solution": "Disable the whitelist.",
  "enable-authentication-solution": "Enable the online authentication."
}